{
    "id": "5184eca2c7d24d57a1f224512fbcee25",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I’m right, ………………..?",
            "description": "The question tag for I’m is aren’t I.",
            "answers": [
                "am I",
                "am'nt I",
                "aren't I"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "69de5f6afa864086bd3c0c3f7d4ea226"
        },
        {
            "question": "Shut up, …………………?",
            "description": "After imperatives will you, would you, can you, can’t you or couldn’t you can be used to tell people to do things.",
            "answers": [
                "can't you",
                "can you",
                "will you",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "5a47f21e9e584878ae379f245f9e1da7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t forget, ………………?",
            "description": "After negative imperatives, we use ‘will you?’",
            "answers": [
                "will you",
                "won't you",
                "can you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ccbab431eeb4eb4896b01a3f8b7d82a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Move a bit, ……………..?",
            "description": "After imperatives will you, would you, can you, can’t you or couldn’t you can be used to tell people to do things.",
            "answers": [
                "will you",
                "would you",
                "can you",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "e19ab1edb6a04c8b8c61927a99d93227"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go for a walk, …………………?",
            "description": "After let’s we use ‘shall we?’",
            "answers": [
                "should we",
                "shall we",
                "can we"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b33aca75daee468da766383963cf5c68"
        },
        {
            "question": "You never say what you are going, …………………?",
            "description": "Non-negative tags are used after negative words like never, no, nobody, hardly etc.",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "029f1cfcc0b7489d882b90d68d09f4d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is little we can do about it, ……………….?",
            "description": "Non-negative tags are used after negative words like never, no, little, nobody, hardly etc.",
            "answers": [
                "is there",
                "isn't there",
                "has there"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58381668f1454ef0b6d8d7ebc8a07cab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody wanted a pizza, …………………..?",
            "description": "We use they to refer to somebody, nobody and everybody.",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they",
                "hadn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76f903e2a5d0421e87c6d654fdab5b47"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a daughter, ………………..?",
            "description": "When have is used as a main verb, question tags with both have and do are possible.",
            "answers": [
                "has he",
                "does he",
                "hasn't he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "268fdb7d244943e19e648674c149bf92"
        },
        {
            "question": "There weren’t any issues, ………………..?",
            "description": "There can be used as a subject in question tags.",
            "answers": [
                "were there",
                "weren't there",
                "were they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3540c41f7bc842cb9f7ff4d908c9b6e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ravi wants to be an actor, ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "hasn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d67853b6ba194b2896262a6921ad5d46"
        },
        {
            "question": "Julia visited you yesterday, ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did she",
                "didn't she",
                "doesn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7113ab4e11524810b8ed1c73ce98f501"
        }
    ]
}